I just want to do a quick message to
jenna Marbles however I know she's not
gonna watch this
so really to anyone else who watches
jenna Marbles and has found this channel
we live in a very backward society
everything that is out there right now
is telling you that happiness and
success comes from getting more
influence more people following you
liking your Instagram posts liking
retweeting your tweets and my friends
with you on Facebook I'm old here's the
thing you don't actually get happiness
from having followers from having people
who love you they get happiness from it
when we feel love for a celebrity we get
the love not you so why are we all
seeking to be the person that everybody
loves when it is a very lonely place to
be when a handful of people who
subscribe to you start throwing anger
and hatred towards you for whatever
reason even if it's earned it feels like
everybody hates you we don't do the same
with love we don't multiply the person
who's like oh my god I love you times a
million we do the negative ones but the
bigger piece is just how love works in
your body to feel love for another human
being you get happiness you get oxytocin
coursing through your veins
it's the love I have for my child it's
not minimized just because it's a
hormone it is real and true and I would
die for her and I get it because I love
her
not because she loves me and so the more
we can concentrate on figuring out how
to love our fellow human beings
the better and happier we will be
luckily we have a event I'm playing with
this weekend where we are trying to fall
in love with another human being not
monogamy hold on to you forever love
just see the other human being in front
of you and fall in love the more we can
figure out how to take away broadcast as
our biggest modality in the
yeah it's really cool that someone could
start a YouTube channel and getting 20
million followers
however we are paying the price for this
in society people that don't understand
things are acting like experts I might
be one of those people but what we need
is more interconnectedness more
distributed influence so that it isn't
one person telling 20 million people how
to live their life even if that's not
her intention it's 20 million people
having conversations with 20 million
people hopefully really truly seeing the
human being in front of them and falling
in love because love on that scale 20
million people falling in love with 20
million on a one-on-one basis
ten million fall in love with ten
million exponentially increases
happiness in the world and then once
you've fallen in love with enough human
beings
you can exponentially increase that you
can say like I've sat with ten human
beings and they were all amazing in HoN
some level I guarantee you every human
being is amazing on some level then we
don't need to try and be the influencer
and the celebrity we can find the peace
of our self that was reflected in that
person that we fell in love with because
that's all anyone is is a reflection of
the good and bad in us and so when
someone makes you feel gross and
disgusting because they did something
even if it was horrific there's
something for you to learn from it we're
really great at hurling insults and
frustration at people we think are doing
worse than we are because we don't want
to sit with our own drama and our own
issues and it happens constantly
right now we are pointing the finger at
people who are more racist than us so we
don't have to deal with their own racism
people that are more sexist than us so
we don't have to deal with their own
sexism
I love the couldn't be racist I'm
married to a black man like oh I guess
sexism isn't a thing then because with
the head of a normativity around you all
are married to women and yet seem to
have not gotten over the misogyny so
loving one person doesn't equal loving
the entire group
it doesn't mean seeing the person
in front of you and if we're in monogamy
you could only love one other person
what do you do with the rest or as if we
can sit with people who are like us sit
with people who are not like us and
learn to fall in love with them we can
grow a society that is full of love and
actual connection one that is resilient
that isn't canceled culture that isn't
you do one thing wrong this generation
my kids generation my kid wants to be an
influencer a - it's like her dream or
she wants a youtube channel if she has
and subscribers I can't just negate that
because there's something there for her
but the thought of her having her
self-worth determined by strangers on
the other end of a screen and then
trying to change herself to be liked by
them is heartbreaking and there's an
entire generation that was raised long
before she was who was raised in the
public eye raised with revenge porn as a
normal part of high school high school
and the actual solution to revenge porn
to me is like right if everyone has it
out there there's no such thing it's not
a big deal why shame why do any of
that like yeah there's new pictures who
cares shouldn't stop you from being the
president on States not if we all have
them that for the person who has never
ever ever taken a nude photo and said
did it someone oh but the solution is in
this generation to figure out instead of
having one person and who broadcasts and
has a ton of influence how do we connect
to that how do we find real deep
connection how do we give ourselves
permission to fall in love with people
instead of meeting everyone to fall in
love with us it is one of the biggest
jokes of the universe that all we want
to do is have people love us and yet all
of the joy comes from when we love other
people and hopefully there's a social
media platform eventually on the way or
you can log on and anytime connect with
somebody and see them as a human being
on video chat and answer 36 questions or
our equivalent is the New York Times
does known and fall in love and do that
on repeat and see how beautiful and
amazing all of the human beings are and
then we won't feel the need to like grab
on to one as love or hate you can be
your own influencer it doesn't take two
hundred billion lovers she's giving up
her channel if she wants to give it to
me I'll save the world but the bigger
piece of that is I am deeply happy on
YouTube right now I have 200 subscribers
not even actually it's just under 200
but it's not these I have 20 to 50 of
those subscribers are people I talk to
on a weekly basis people who support my
vision won't cancel me because they will
have a conversation with me
I feel actual love for them because I
can see who they are as human beings it
doesn't even matter if you love as I can
I feel a lot for me it doesn't matter I
love them and so I don't want to keep
this any longer than it than it is right
now this is the quality of my youtube
videos please like it subscribe if you
found this through the jenna Marbles I
am creating a world that works for
everyone I'm figuring out how do we do
deep personal connection how do we have
conversations about our solution
raisings on this channel is a powerful
way that we can create solutions
together without influence or deciding
what those solutions are ten thousand
people having conversations and we can
vote up the best one our new project
this weekend we're doing on Zoom for
oxytocin 36 billion oxytocin in your own
body
and the bigger part is I'm here to play
I am here to find out what works and
what doesn't and live my own life the
other thing with the jenna Marbles
videos she was constantly constantly
like I don't want to offend anyone I'm
like well you can't you literally can't
be in the world and not offend someone
because anything you say is gonna offend
someone together unless it's so freaking
vanilla it makes us all one puke if it's
any kind of controversial any kind of
funny it's gonna if offend anyone so so
unless it's truly something that feels
like
that's wrong and it feels wrong in your
own body then you need to look at what
you did it and correct it and then
forgive yourself and if it's someone
else reflecting it back at you that is
what our culture currently is you didn't
sit the wrong thing and you're cancelled
well why was it wrong who are the right
people to offend you who are the wrong
people to offend and how offended and
then are we gonna go back 10 years
liquid offense we need a new way we need
a way that people feel safe because
nobody feels safe right now and that is
my comments so Jenna marble anyone who's
Jenna marble fan you have to find a way
to contact me because I don't really
you'll probably know how do I miss thing
um you're invited oxytocin 36 come fall
in love with an actual human being in
front of you guarantee you my friends
and family won't know who you are they
will not be in celebrity status you're
like oh another human being they might
know you if you tell them through your
name I don't know but come fall in love
with another human being
and let's just grow it exponentially
until we all know that love is not a
scarce resource it is everywhere and
everybody is lovable all we have to do
is allow it thank you